<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Edison, NJ</string>
    <string name="app_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="app_corporations">Corporations</string>
    <string name="app_historical_places">Historical Places</string>
    <string name="app_communities">Communities</string>
    <string name="bonhamtown">BonhamTown</string>
    <string name="clarabarton">Clara Barton</string>
    <string name="lindenau">Lindenau</string>
    <string name="menlopark">Menlo Park</string>
    <string name="nixon">Nixon</string>
    <string name="pumptown">Pumptown</string>
    <string name="majesco">Majesco Entertainment</string>
    <string name="colavita">Colavita</string>
    <string name="zylog">Zylog Systems</string>
    <string name="boxed">Boxed</string>
    <string name="benjamin">Benjamin House</string>
    <string name="homesteadfarm">Homestead Farm</string>
    <string name="lainghouse">Laing House</string>
    <string name="roosevelt">Roosevelt County Park</string>
    <string name="edisonpark">Thomas Edison County Park</string>
    <string name="rutgers">Rutgers Gardens</string>
    <string name="papaianni">Papaianni Park</string>
    <string name="roosevelt_info">Roosevelt Park is one of the many expansive parks in the New Jersey suburbs. No matter the weather there is always something to do at the park.</string>
    <string name="edison_info"><![CDATA[Not to be confused with the museum in West Orange, this 171-acre county park is adjacent to both Middlesex County College & Raritan Center.]]></string>
    <string name="rutgers_info">This park has giant green chairs with a beautiful garden and a bamboo forest.</string>
    <string name="papaianni_info">Decent park with a small lake with fountain, a couple baseball diamonds, a soccer field, a skate park and some picnics tables in the woods.</string>
    <string name="bonham_info">Bonhamtown is an unincorporated community located within Edison Township in Middlesex County, New Jersey, United States. The area was named after Nicholas Bonham, a freeholder from the 17th century.</string>
    <string name="clara_info">Clara Barton is an unincorporated community located within Edison Township in Middlesex County, New Jersey, United States.</string>
    <string name="lindenau_info">Lindenau is an unincorporated community located within Edison Township in Middlesex County, New Jersey, United States.</string>
    <string name="menlopark_info">In 1876, Thomas Edison set up his home and research laboratory in Menlo Park, which at the time was the site of an unsuccessful real estate development named after the town of Menlo Park, California.</string>
    <string name="nixon_info">Nixon is an unincorporated community located within Edison Township in Middlesex County, New Jersey, United States. It was named after Lewis Nixon, a manufacturer and community leader.</string>
    <string name="pumptown_info">Pumptown is an unincorporated community located within Edison Township in Middlesex County, New Jersey, United States. Pumptown is a suburban neighborhood (based on population density) located in Edison, New Jersey.</string>
    <string name="majesco_info">A video game company headquartered in Edison</string>
    <string name="colavita_info">Italian Food Importer and Producer</string>
    <string name="zylog_info">The international HQ in US is in Edison</string>
    <string name="boxed_info">E-commerce company headquartered in Edison</string>
    <string name="benjamin_info">The Benjamin Shotwell House, or the Shotwell-Runyon House, is a historic house in Edison, Middlesex County, New Jersey. The house was listed on the New Jersey Register of Historic Places and National Register of Historic Places in 1987. The farm on which is located in part of Route 287. The Shotwells were early settlers of \"The Plains\", an early reference to Plainfield, New Jersey.</string>
    <string name="homesteadfarm_info">Homestead Farm at Oak Ridge is a historic home and grounds in Clark (Union County) and Edison (Middlesex County), New Jersey, United States, that was listed on the New Jersey Register of Historic Places and National Register of Historic Places in 1995. The c. 1750 building and site is located what was once Ash Swamp that played a pivotal role in the American Revolutionary War Battle of Short Hills.</string>
    <string name="lainghouse_info">Laing House of Plainfield Plantation is a historic house in Edison, Middlesex County, New Jersey, United States, built in the early 18th century when the region was being settled by Scottish Quakers in the late 17th and early 18th century, as recalled in the name of The Plainfields and Scotch Plains.The region was part of the colonial era Elizabethtown Tract and later part of Piscataway Township.</string>
</resources>
